[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the director of the successful Pirates of the Caribbean movies.", "correct_answer": "Gore Verbinski", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Siegel", "Spike Jonze", "Nora Ephron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Kramer vs Kramer was released in 1978.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the capital city of the U.S. state of Montana.", "correct_answer": "Helena", "incorrect_answers": ["Billings", "Pierre", "Sioux Falls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the diet of most penguin species primarily consist of?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Krill", "Squid", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What reportedly happened to actress Halle Berry while shooting a fight scene for the 2006 movie X-Men: The Last Stand?", "correct_answer": "She vomited.", "incorrect_answers": ["She broke her wrist.", "All of these", "She fell down from a considerable height."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This type of tobacco is the mildest of all blending tobaccos and has the highest level of natural dextrose.", "correct_answer": "Virginia", "incorrect_answers": ["Perique", "Burley", "Latakia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many pecks are there in a bushel?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "10", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Groundhogs are mostly herbivorous rodents that sometimes eat animal matter. What kind of animals would they feed on?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Larvae", "Grasshoppers", "Snails"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Back to the Future, in 1955 Martys parents were supposed to go  a school dance, named what?", "correct_answer": "Enchantment Under the Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Enchanted Future", "Sadie Hawkins Day Dance", "Fish Under the Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Regina in the movie Mean Girls, after Janis reveals that she and Cady plotted to destroy Reginas queen bee status?", "correct_answer": "She is hit by a bus.", "incorrect_answers": ["She steals Cadys boyfriend.", "She becomes a modern day Mother Theresa.", "She moves to Australia."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Buddhism, a religion and philosophy based on the teachings of Siddh\u0101rtha Gautama, traces its origins to which country?", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["Taiwan", "Thailand", "China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many eggs are in 1 gross?", "correct_answer": "144", "incorrect_answers": ["96", "12", "48"]}]